zannel.com 2011-02-12

# Zannel » privacy

## Zannel, Inc. Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Zannel, Inc.’s (“Zannel”) Internet web site (“Site”) located at the URL [http://www.Zannel.com](http://www.zannel.com/). At Zannel, we value your privacy and we want you to feel comfortable by telling you what we do to help protect your privacy and improve your experience using our Site and Services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personally identifiable information of the users of our Site and the web plug-in, desktop, wap, mobile application and other services (collectively, the “Services”) provided by Zannel via this Site or otherwise.

#### Privacy Policy Updates

Due to the Internet’s rapidly evolving nature, Zannel may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, Zannel will post its updated Privacy Policy on our Site located at [http://www.Zannel.com](http://www.zannel.com/) so you are always aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use or disclose this information. Zannel encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site or our Service and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

#### Information Collection and Use

You can generally visit our Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, in certain sections of this Site, we may require you to register to use our Services, contact us with questions or comments or request information, participate in contests, surveys or questionnaires. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may collect personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, phone number, password, username, gender, age, employment, income level, credit card information, phone carrier, phone model, mobile browser type, device firmware version and any other information that you voluntarily transmit during your communications to us. Additionally, we may collect personally identifiable information about you that you voluntarily include or post in any content that you submit to the Site and/or through the use of the Services and other users will be able to see any information that you include in your content and such publicly available forums. Thus, you should be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information, that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to contact you or to communicate with you. Therefore, we encourage you think about what personally identifiable information you include in your postings and/or submissions to this Site. We may use your personally identifiable information to deliver certain Services, products or information you have requested, send you notices for products and/or Services that you have used or that may be of interest to you and other marketing materials, and improve the content and general administration of the Site and our Services.

Additionally, we may track your usage of our Site and Services. Through such tracking, we also may collect information about you and your use of our Site and Services such as the content you have posted or viewed. To the extent you have opted in to this feature, other users may be able to run searches that reveal information about you and the content you have viewed (based on the search criteria entered by the other users like age, gender, types of content and so forth) and such users may instant message you using our Services.

#### Children’s Privacy

Zannel recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. No personally identifiable information is collected by Zannel from children under the age of 13 and this Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. Zannel does not target its Services or this Site to children under 13. Zannel does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

#### Cookies

We may use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you. 

#### Aggregate Information

The Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, IP addresses, External Web Sites (defined below) linked to, and we may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

#### Disclosure

We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. We may provide your personally identifiable information that we collect and the data generated by cookies to our parent, subsidiary or affiliate entities within our corporate family, third party partner entities and the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us. For example, we may provide your personally identifiable information to an organization in order to complete a service (e.g., process your payment). Such third party entities will be restricted from further distributing your personally identifiable information and they will not be permitted to further distribute your personally identifiable information. However, certain third party entities with whom we have a business relationship may use your personally identifiable information to send you marketing or promotional materials. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any company or organization except we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Zannel participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Zannel’s assets to which this Site relates.

#### Links to Third Party Sites

The Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which Zannel does not have control (“External Web Sites”). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Zannel of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that Zannel is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that Zannel is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.

#### Security

We may employ procedural and technological measures, consistent with industry practice. Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Zannel may use password protection, secured private networks and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

#### Questions

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us via email at: [biz@zannel.com](mailto:biz@zannel.com)

This Privacy Policy was last updated:  **October 24, 2006**  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of: **October 24, 2006**
